# EMILIANO -—ALFONSO

#### WEB DEVELOPER

### **ABOUT ME**

Music teacher and front-end fanatic who enjoys learning new technologies, creating beautiful websites and overall making the user have a good experience. When it comes to designing, I am a perfectionist. I am a person that's easy to get along with, and am always striving to be a better dev.

### **EXPERIENCE**

**Fullstack Developer at Distrocuyo S.A.** (mar 2021 - present) - Development of web apps related to electricity and assets from that field.

**Teaching Assistant at Henry** (dec. 2020 - feb. 2021, may. 2021 - present) - My role is to guide students, help them understand core concepts and reinforce the theory by providing explanations and extracurricular projects.

**E-commerce Project** (dec. 2020 - jan. 2021) - Design and development of a website dedicated to selling digital videogames. Built using React, Redux, Express, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, Passport, and Flrebase.

#### **EDUCATION**

"Luis Gianneo" College of Music, Mar del Plata (dec. 2010 - dec. 2020) - Music Teacher

Henry Bootcamp (oct. 2020 - feb. 2021) - Fullstack Developer. 700+ hours of intensive learning. The technologies learned there include HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Redux, Node, Express, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, Github, and the SCRUM methodology.

## SKILLS AND SOFTWARE

HTML	Bootstrap	React	Node.js	PostgreSQL	Adobe XD
CSS	Less & Sass	Redux	Express	Git & Github	Adobe Photoshop
JavaScript	Tailwind CSS	Next.js	Sequelize	Testing	

# CONTACT